<?xml version="1.0" ?>

<list>
<!-- Inventory items-->
<text>
	<id>0</id>
	<name>
</name>
</text>

<!--Canned Beans-->
<text>
	<id>1</id>
	<name>A nutritious and long-lasting can of baked beans. Will last two to five years depending on storage conditions.

Hunger: +30
Thirst: +5
</name>
</text>

<!--Canned Tuna-->
<text>
	<id>2</id>
	<name>A can of tuna. If unopened, it will last two to five years depending on storage conditions.

Hunger: +20
</name>
</text>

<!--Tactical Bacon-->
<text>
	<id>3</id>
	<name>A can of bacon. Smoke flavor added! Fully cooked! Delicious. Unopened, it lasts over 10 years.

Hunger: +35
</name>
</text>

<!--Rice-->
<text>
	<id>4</id>
	<name>A bag of long-grained rice, usually consumed when cooked with water. Conveniently packed for easier preparation.

Hunger: +65
</name>
</text>

<!--Tomato-->
<text>
	<id>5</id>
	<name>A tomato. If we leave the fruit-vegetable debate aside, it is still tasty and edible, either raw, or cooked.

Hunger: +15
Thirst: +5
Max Stack: 3
Ingredient for: Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--Apple-->
<text>
	<id>6</id>
	<name>An ordinary ripe apple. It is still firm, delicious, and worm-free.

Hunger: +15
Thirst: +5
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Banana-->
<text>
	<id>7</id>
	<name>A fresh banana, rich in potassium.

Hunger: +15
Thirst: +5
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Pipsi-->
<text>
	<id>8</id>
	<name>A comparatively unhealthy, [cola flavored] beverage, alternative to water - containing carbonated water, sweeteners, flavoring agents, coloring agents and preservatives.

Thirst: +30
</name>
</text>

<!--Spite-->
<text>
	<id>9</id>
	<name>A comparatively unhealthy, [lemon-lime flavored] beverage, alternative to water - containing carbonated water, sweeteners, flavoring agents, coloring agents and preservatives.

Thirst: +30
</name>
</text>

<!--Kvas-->
<text>
	<id>10</id>
	<name>A healthy, [fermented] beverage made from rye bread, tasty and delicious.

Thirst: +50
</name>
</text>

<!--5.56x45 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>11</id>
	<name>5.56x45mm NATO intermediate cartridge. Used in select rifles and LMGs.

Chambered in: M4, M16A2, L85, AUG, FAMAS, Mini-14, M249
Max Stack: 50
</name>
</text>

<!--.45 ACP Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>12</id>
	<name>.45 ACP pistol cartridge. Used in select pistols and SMGs.

Chambered in: FNX, Colt 1911, UMP-45, Vector, Mini-UZI
Max Stack: 60
</name>
</text>

<!--7.62x54R Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>13</id>
	<name>7.62x54mmR full power cartridge. Used in select rifles and LMGs.

Chambered in: Mosin-Nagant, Sawn-off Mosin, SVD, SV-98
Max Stack: 40
</name>
</text>

<!--7.62x39 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>14</id>
	<name>7.62x39mm intermediate cartridge. Used in select rifles and LMGs.

Chambered in: SKS, AKM, RPK
Max Stack: 50
</name>
</text>

<!--5.45x39 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>15</id>
	<name>5.45x39mm intermediate cartridge. Used in select rifles.

Chambered in: AKs-74u, AK-74, AN-94
Max Stack: 50
</name>
</text>

<!--.357 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>16</id>
	<name>.357 M revolver cartridge. Used in select pistols, revolvers, and rifles.

Chambered in: Magnum, Desert Eagle, Rossi M92, Sawn-off Rossi M92
Max Stack: 50
</name>
</text>

<!--12 Gauge Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>17</id>
	<name>12 Gauge buck shell with 5 pellets. Used in shotguns.

Chambered in: IZH-43, Sawn-off IZH-43, Remington, Saiga-12k
Max Stack: 30
</name>
</text>

<!--Bandage-->
<text>
	<id>18</id>
	<name>A roll of sterile gauze bandage. Can be used to directly stop the bleeding.

Apply Time: 2 sec
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Blood Bag-->
<text>
	<id>19</id>
	<name>A bag of whole blood [O−] with an IV set ready for transfusion. Single use to replace blood lost due to bleeding.

Health: +50
Immunity: +50
Apply Time: 6 sec
</name>
</text>

<!--Flare-->
<text>
	<id>20</id>
	<name>Provides a small radius of bright red light for a brief time. Can be thrown to light up an area and attract zombies when it burns.

Effect Duration: 90 sec
Max Stack: 5
Ingredient for: Molotov Cocktail
</name>
</text>

<!--F1 Grenade-->
<text>
	<id>21</id>
	<name>Fragmentation grenade type used by the Russian forces. It is lethal in a small radius, but can cause serious injuries at medium ranges.

Damage: 1800             Damage per Fragment: 75
Fuse Time: 2 sec          Fragments: 24
</name>
</text>

<!--Battery-->
<text>
	<id>22</id>
	<name>A common 9V battery, used to power various electronic devices.
</name>
</text>

<!--Campfire Kit-->
<text>
	<id>23</id>
	<name>A bundle of wood and kindling ready to be assembled. After deploying, can be used up to 3 times, each lasting 3 minutes.
</name>
</text>

<!--Matches-->
<text>
	<id>24</id>
	<name>A box of long kitchen safety matches to light a flame on demand. Store in a dry place and keep away from children.

Can light a campfire kit or cigarettes.
</name>
</text>

<!--Whiskey-->
<text>
	<id>25</id>
	<name>"I've drunk whiskey, I feel healthy."

Thirst: +20
Temperature: +40
Ingredient for: Molotov Cocktail
</name>
</text>

<!--Rags-->
<text>
	<id>26</id>
	<name>An assortment of torn rags, still... can be used to stop bleeding.

Apply Time: 5 sec
Max Stack: 3
Ingredient for: Campfire Kit, Rope
</name>
</text>

<!--Cranberries-->
<text>
	<id>27</id>
	<name>Cranberries can be collected from the berry bushes found throughout the forests. They can be distinguished easily by their red, ripe and juicy berries.

Hunger: +15
Thirst: +15
Max Stack: 5
</name>
</text>

<!--Saline Bag-->
<text>
	<id>28</id>
	<name>A bag of saline solution with an IV set ready for transfusion. Used to replace some blood lost due to bleeding.

Health: +25
Immunity: +25
Apply Time: 6 sec
</name>
</text>

<!--Vitamins-->
<text>
	<id>29</id>
	<name>Multi-Vitamin supplements help boost blood to recover health twice as fast.

Immunity: +10
Health Regen: x2
Effect Duration: 60 sec
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Nota-Cola-->
<text>
	<id>30</id>
	<name>A comparatively unhealthy, [cola flavored] beverage, alternative to water - containing carbonated water, sweeteners, flavoring agents, coloring agents and preservatives.

Thirst: +30
</name>
</text>

<!--Zucchini-->
<text>
	<id>31</id>
	<name>This zucchini is just ripe enough to be eaten raw.

Hunger: +20
Thirst: +20
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--Bell Pepper-->
<text>
	<id>32</id>
	<name>Bell pepper, green variety. Not so spicy and has plenty of nutrients and vitamins, can be used for cooking or eaten raw.

Hunger: +20
Thirst: +5
Max Stack: 3
Ingredient for: Pepper Steak
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--Orange-->
<text>
	<id>33</id>
	<name>A popular citrus fruit, packed with vitamin "C".

Hunger: +15
Thirst: +15
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Heat Pack-->
<text>
	<id>34</id>
	<name>A small disposable heat source. Keeps you warm for a limited time when put into a jacket, pants or vest.

Temperature: +25
</name>
</text>

<!--Sewing Kit-->
<text>
	<id>35</id>
	<name>A pocket-sized universal sewing kit, comes in handy for patching various clothes.

Can restore 50% durability to clothing and some hats.
</name>
</text>

<!--Cleaning Kit-->
<text>
	<id>36</id>
	<name>A wooden box containing a complete and universal gun-care system.

Can restore 25% durability to firearms.
</name>
</text>

<!--Ash Wood Stick-->
<text>
	<id>37</id>
	<name>A firm but flexible long wooden branch from the native ashwood trees.

Ingredient for: Makeshift Fishing Rod, Bow
</name>
</text>

<!--Stick-->
<text>
	<id>38</id>
	<name>Multipurpose pieces of wood. Ideal for making arrows, kindling, and barricades. Drops from the native ashwood trees.

Max Stack: 5
Ingredient for: Campfire Kit, Handmade Arrows, Makeshift Backpack, Wooden Fence
</name>
</text>

<!--Duct Tape-->
<text>
	<id>39</id>
	<name>A versatile, strong and flexible wide adhesive tape. If it moves and shouldn't, use duct tape.

Can repair 15% durability of clothes.
Ingredient for: Makeshift Suppressor
</name>
</text>

<!--Sack-->
<text>
	<id>40</id>
	<name>A burlap sack, ideal for shipping and storing stuff. A drawstring closure can be improvised at the top of the bag using a rope.

Ingredient for: Makeshift Backpack, Tarpaulin
</name>
</text>

<!--Rope-->
<text>
	<id>41</id>
	<name>A strong rope, used to tie stuff together, be it things or people.

Can be attached to the waist as an accessory to carry an additional melee weapon.
Ingredient for: Makeshift Backpack, Bow, Makeshift Fishing Rod
</name>
</text>

<!--Hunting Knife-->
<text>
	<id>42</id>
	<name>The hunting knife is a specialized tool designed with a slightly curved tip, primarily for field dressing game.

Damage: 14-24
Crit Chance: 10%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!--Army Knife-->
<text>
	<id>43</id>
	<name>A sharp combat knife with a sturdy blade and handle. Great for self-defense, but it has other, more mundane uses as well.

Damage: 15-25
Crit Chance: 15%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!--Butcher Knife-->
<text>
	<id>44</id>
	<name>A big, heavy, rusted knife. Designed to slash through thick raw meat. It can also crack bones easily. Mostly used by butchers.

Damage: 16-26
Crit Chance: 20%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!--Morphine-->
<text>
	<id>45</id>
	<name>Morphine prepares your body for "fight or flight" situations by increasing heart rate, blood flow, and alertness.

Immunity: -10
Drug Effect: Temporary invincibility and +20% movement speed
Duration: 20 sec (health drops to 10% when effect ends)
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Tetracycline-->
<text>
	<id>46</id>
	<name>Broad spectrum antibiotics. Used to treat viral and bacterial infectious diseases and prevents sickness.

Immunity: +10
Drug Effect: Cures and prevents sickness and poisoning for the effect duration
Effect Duration: 60 sec
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!--Tomato Seeds-->
<text>
	<id>47</id>
	<name>The text on the pack says: "A useful variety for outdoor cultivation in even the wet summers! Grow these vigorous, indeterminate plants to produce heavy crops of deep red fruits with a very good flavor".

Uses: 5
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork, or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--Bell Pepper Seeds-->
<text>
	<id>48</id>
	<name>The text on the pack says: "A large bell pepper and a great variety for classic bell pepper taste. Bears large fruits with a blocky shape. Usually eaten while green, fruits have a sweet flavor and crunchy texture".

Uses: 5
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork, or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--Newspaper-->
<text>
	<id>49</id>
	<name>Everyday newspapers found in homes before the apocalypse. They still contain useful crafts, guides and articles about survival and can be read to gain some experience.

Experience: +50
Ingredient for: Campfire Kit
</name>
</text>

<!--Wood-->
<text>
	<id>50</id>
	<name>Its wood, the basic survival material. Can be obtained by chopping up a tree using axes or bladed weapons.

Ingredient for: Campfire Kit, Wooden Fence, Supply Cache, Metal Fence
</name>
</text>

<!--Handmade Arrow-->
<text>
	<id>51</id>
	<name>Wooden sticks carved using knives into finely matched arrows, but they are flimsy.

Damage: 37-63
Max Stack: 10
75% chance to break after firing.
Can be loaded into: Bow, Hunting Crossbow
</name>
</text>

<!--Composite Arrow-->
<text>
	<id>52</id>
	<name>Modern aluminum core composite bolts with high impact.

Damage: 56-94
Max Stack: 10
Will not break after firing.
Can be loaded into: Bow, Hunting Crossbow
</name>
</text>

<!--Gas Can-->
<text>
	<id>53</id>
	<name>A metal canister, filled with large volumes of gasoline.

Provides 25% fuel for vehicles, chainsaws, and generators per use
</name>
</text>

<!--Water Bottle-->
<text>
	<id>54</id>
	<name>A common reusable plastic bottle. Can be filled with water from water pumps.

Thirst: +12
Uses: 4
Can be filled with water from a pump
Can collect rainwater when left on the ground while raining
Ingredient for: Makeshift Suppressor
</name>
</text>

<!--Canteen-->
<text>
	<id>55</id>
	<name>A reusable military grade plastic bottle used by the army and campers. Can be filled with water from water pumps.

Thirst: +25
Uses: 4
Can be filled with water from a pump
</name>
</text>

<!--Landmine-->
<text>
	<id>56</id>
	<name>Anti-personnel mine. Provides a nasty surprise for anybody unlucky enough to step on it.

Damage: 1800          Damage per Fragment: 75
Fragments: 24
Explodes when triggered by entities other than you and your teammates.
</name>
</text>

<!--Bear Trap-->
<text>
	<id>57</id>
	<name>Old-fashioned but functional, this marvel of mechanical engineering can almost snap your leg in half.

Damage: 200
Can be reused again
Not triggered by the player
</name>
</text>

<!--.22 LR Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>58</id>
	<name>.22 Long rifle rimfire cartridge. Used in small pistols and rifles.

Chambered in: Sporter22, MK II
Max Stack: 80
</name>
</text>

<!--Vehicle Repair Kit-->
<text>
	<id>59</id>
	<name>A toolkit containing mechanical tools that can be used for repairing and restoring damaged vehicles.

Can repair 25% durability of vehicles.
</name>
</text>

<!--Raw Steak-->
<text>
	<id>60</id>
	<name>A raw chunk of meat from a deer. Tougher, darker meat, it can be quite tasty once prepared.

Hunger: +25
Thirst: +10
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a campfire
Ingredient for: Pepper Steak
</name>
</text>

<!--Cooked Steak-->
<text>
	<id>61</id>
	<name>Raw venison steak roasted over a campfire to succulent perfection.

Hunger: +50
Thirst: +10
Health: +15
</name>
</text>

<!--Nuka-Cola-->
<text>
	<id>62</id>
	<name>A bottle of Nuka-Cola, the flavored soft drink of the post-nuclear world. Warm and flat. Invigorating, refreshing Nukem.

Thirst: +100
Experience: +200
Health Regen: x2
Effect Duration: 60 sec
</name>
</text>

<!--Energy Drink-->
<text>
	<id>63</id>
	<name>A straightforward option for a bolt of athletic energy, it combines caffeine, vitamins, and a familiar Mountain Dew taste.

Thirst: +20
Movement Speed: +15%
Effect Duration: 20 sec
</name>
</text>

<!--Zucchini Seeds-->
<text>
	<id>68</id>
	<name>The text on the pack says: "This is our most popular zucchini. An early, very productive, bushy plant with an open habit. The flesh is delicious, creamy white, tender and firm".

Uses: 5
Can be planted with a pickaxe, pitchfork or shovel
</name>
</text>

<!--9mm Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>69</id>
	<name>9x19mm Parabellum pistol cartridge. Used in select pistols and SMGs.

Chambered in: Glock, MP5, MAC-10
Max Stack: 60
</name>
</text>

<!--Barbed Wire-->
<text>
	<id>70</id>
	<name>A roll of gnarly barbed wire made for fencing off walls and barriers.

Deals minor damage and slows enemies by 2 seconds when triggered.
Ingredient for: Barbed Wire Baseball Bat
</name>
</text>

<!--Raw Rabbit Meat-->
<text>
	<id>71</id>
	<name>The posterior leg of a rabbit. When cooked provides quite a tasty snack.

Hunger: +25
Thirst: +10
Ingredient for: Pepper Steak
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a campfire
</name>
</text>

<!--Cooked Rabbit Meat-->
<text>
	<id>72</id>
	<name>Rabbit leg roasted over a campfire, tender and flavorful.

Hunger: +35
Thirst: +10
Health: +30
</name>
</text>

<!--Cloudberries-->
<text>
	<id>73</id>
	<name>Cloudberries can only be found around lakes. Although very healthy, this unusual berry gives off a musky odor.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +10
Health Regen: x2
Effect Duration: 30 sec
Max Stack: 5
</name>
</text>

<!--Raspberries-->
<text>
	<id>74</id>
	<name>Raspberries can be collected from the berry bushes found throughout the forests. These berries are juicy with high water content.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +20
Max Stack: 5
</name>
</text>

<!--Radio-->
<text>
	<id>75</id>
	<name>A device, such as a walkie-talkie, that transmits or receives radio signals. Its current set frequency picks up the faint radio signals of crashed military transports.

Reveals nearby military crash sites
Each use consumes 10% battery charge
</name>
</text>

<!--RDS-->
<text>
	<id>76</id>
	<name>A standardized rail-mounted, non-magnifying optic with a red dot projected onto the lens.

Spread: -1
Headshot Chance: +5%
Fits on: MP5, UMP-45, Vector, AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, M4, M16A2, L85, FN-FAL, RPK, Saiga-12k, Bizon, Groza, VSS, SV-98, Mini-14, AS-VAL, M249, Hunting Crossbow
</name>
</text>

<!--PU Scope-->
<text>
	<id>77</id>
	<name>A 3.5x scope of Soviet manufacture from the WW2 era.

Spread: -2
Headshot Chance: +15%
Aiming Distance: +20%
Fits on: SKS, Mosin-Nagant, M70, Blaze
</name>
</text>

<!--PSO-1 Scope-->
<text>
	<id>78</id>
	<name>A marksman telescopic sight with fixed 4x magnification and ballistic compensation in range from 100m to 1000m.

Spread: -2
Headshot Chance: +15%
Aiming Distance: +20%
Fits on: AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, RPK, Bizon, Groza, VSS
</name>
</text>

<!--ACOG Scope-->
<text>
	<id>79</id>
	<name>Advanced Combat Optical Gunsight with 4x magnification level. Attachable to any weapon with a standardized rail system.

Spread: -2
Headshot Chance: +15%
Aiming Distance: +20%
Fits on: MP5, UMP-45, Vector, M4, M16A2, L85, FN-FAL, SV-98, Mini-14, AS-VAL, M249, Hunting Crossbow
</name>
</text>

<!--5.45 Suppressor-->
<text>
	<id>80</id>
	<name>An attachment for the barrel of a firearm that reduces the amount of noise generated by firing. This variant is designed for the 5.45mm caliber.

Suppresses weapon noise
Fits on: AKs-74u, AN-94, Ak-74
</name>
</text>

<!--5.56 Suppressor-->
<text>
	<id>81</id>
	<name>An attachment for the barrel of a firearm that reduces the amount of noise generated by firing. This variant is designed for the 5.56mm caliber.

Suppresses weapon noise
Fits on: M4, M16A2, L85, AUG, M249
</name>
</text>

<!--Hacksaw-->
<text>
	<id>82</id>
	<name>A fine-tooth hand saw with a blade held under tension in a frame, used for cutting materials such as metal or plastics.

Can saw down the barrels of certain firearms.
Can be crafted: Improvised VOG-25 Grenade (requires VOG-25 Grenade)
</name>
</text>

<!--Bandolier-->
<text>
	<id>83</id>
	<name>Attached on the rifle stock, the bandolier is designed to keep ammunition readily available during hunting and combat.

Reload Speed: +30%
Fits on: IZH-43, Remington, SKS, Mosin-Nagant, Rossi M92, M70, Blaze
</name>
</text>

<!--MRE-->
<text>
	<id>85</id>
	<name>Meal Ready-to-Eat [MRE], a self-contained, individual field ration intended for use by the military. These rations are designed to provide a complete, balanced meal for one person.

Hunger: +40
Thirst: +40
Each use reduces capacity by 50%
</name>
</text>

<!--Spinning Fishing Rod-->
<text>
	<id>86</id>
	<name>An extendable fishing rod. Highly portable, it makes fishing seem simple.

Used for fishing
Each use consumes 10% durability
</name>
</text>

<!--Simple Fishing Rod-->
<text>
	<id>87</id>
	<name>A piece of rope tied to a stick. This marvelous invention can be surprisingly useful, but it's very flimsy.

Used for fishing
Each use consumes 25% durability
</name>
</text>

<!--Protective Case-->
<text>
	<id>88</id>
	<name>A lost yellow case sealed with loot, belongs to a group of neutral survivors.

Items lost by survivors
Can be returned to them for goodwill, or kept for yourself
</name>
</text>

<!--Quick-Draw Mag-->
<text>
	<id>89</id>
	<name>Attached at the end of a magazine, it makes easy work to swap magazines from pouches, pockets or bags.

Reload Speed: +30%
Fits on: AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, M4, M16A2, L85, FN-FAL, AUG, RPK, Saiga-12k, Groza, VSS, FAMAS, Mini-14
</name>
</text>

<!--Choke-->
<text>
	<id>90</id>
	<name>The choke constricts the muzzle end of the barrel to alter the shot into a concentrated pattern.

Reduces pellet spread for shotguns
Fits on: IZH-43, Remington, Saiga-12k
</name>
</text>

<!--Herring-->
<text>
	<id>91</id>
	<name>Herring, a small, silvery, forage fish known for its streamlined bodies and iridescent scales.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +10
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a fire
</name>
</text>

<!--Salmon-->
<text>
	<id>92</id>
	<name>Salmon, a diverse group of fish known for its migratory patterns, moving between freshwater and saltwater habitats.

Hunger: +35
Thirst: +15
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a fire
</name>
</text>

<!--Perch-->
<text>
	<id>93</id>
	<name>Perch are known for having two dorsal fins, one spiny and one soft, and are typically carnivorous bottom-dwellers.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +10
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a fire
</name>
</text>

<!--Bass-->
<text>
	<id>94</id>
	<name>Bass is a popular game fish known for its fighting ability and tasty white flesh.

Hunger: +35
Thirst: +15
50% chance of getting sick after consumption
Can be cooked over a fire
</name>
</text>

<!--Small Grilled Fish-->
<text>
	<id>95</id>
	<name>A small fish fillet roasted over a campfire for a tasty, decent sized snack.

Hunger: +25
Thirst: +10
Health: +10
</name>
</text>

<!--Large Grilled Fish-->
<text>
	<id>96</id>
	<name>A prepared fish fillet seared over the campfire. It's fully-cooked, flaky, tender and filling.

Hunger: +50
Thirst: +10
Health: +10
</name>
</text>

<!--Mushroom-->
<text>
	<id>97</id>
	<name>A mysterious mushroom with unusual properties...

The road ahead is rough
</name>
</text>

<!--Long-Range Scope-->
<text>
	<id>98</id>
	<name>A rifle scope with variable zoom. Factory default zeroed to 200m and manually adjustable to 800m.

Spread: -3
Headshot Chance: +25%
Aiming Distance: +50%
Fits on: SKS, Mosin-Nagant, SVD, SV-98, M70, Blaze, Mini-14, FN-FAL, AS-VAL, Hunting Crossbow
</name>
</text>

<!--Claymore-->
<text>
	<id>99</id>
	<name>A directional explosive mine. A convenient label reminds the user to point it toward the enemy.

Damage: 1575          Damage per Fragment: 75
Fragments: 21
Explodes and fires fragments in a specified direction when triggered by anyone except you and your teammates.
</name>
</text>

<!--9x18 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>100</id>
	<name>9x18mm Makarov pistol round. Used in select pistols and SMGs.

Chambered in: PM, PB, Bizon
Max Stack: 60
</name>
</text>

<!--9x39 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>101</id>
	<name>9x39mm intermediate subsonic cartridge. Used in select rifles.

Chambered in: VSS, Groza
Max Stack: 50
</name>
</text>

<!--Molotov Cocktail-->
<text>
	<id>102</id>
	<name>An incendiary Molotov cocktail, improvised by attaching a flare to a bottle of good whiskey. It surprisingly does the job.

Creates a lingering flame on impact, damaging creatures
</name>
</text>

<!--Flare Gun-->
<text>
	<id>103</id>
	<name>A single-use flare gun loaded with a flare cartridge. When fired, it signals for an air drop supply crate of random tier.

Fires a flare into the sky, calling in an airdrop after 20 seconds
Can attract nearby zombies
</name>
</text>

<!--.50 Cal Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>104</id>
	<name>The specific type of .50 caliber ammunition and its availability in belt-fed configurations can be very based, for the application of gun turrets.

Ammo used in the Humvee's gun turret
Can be mounted on the Humvee's machine gun
</name>
</text>

<!--40mm Grenade-->
<text>
	<id>105</id>
	<name>Charges for the M203 under-barrel grenade launcher. Explodes on impact.

Damage: 540          Damage per Fragment: 45
Fragments: 12
Max Stack: 10
Fired from an M203 Grenade Launcher, explodes dealing massive damage
</name>
</text>

<!--VOG-25 Grenade-->
<text>
	<id>106</id>
	<name>Charges for the GP-25 under-barrel grenade launcher. Explodes on impact.

Damage: 540          Damage per Fragment: 45
Fragments: 12
Max Stack: 10
Fired from a GP-25 Grenade Launcher, explodes dealing massive damage
Can be crafted: Improvised VOG-25 Grenade (requires Hacksaw)
</name>
</text>

<!--M203 Grenade Launcher-->
<text>
	<id>107</id>
	<name>The M203 is a single-shot 40mm, muzzle-loaded, under-barrel grenade launcher designed to attach to a rifle. It's a Western-style design.

Grenade launcher for NATO firearms
Can load and fire 40mm grenades
Fits on: M4, M16A2, L85, FN-FAL, FAMAS
</name>
</text>

<!--GP-25 Grenade Launcher-->
<text>
	<id>108</id>
	<name>The GP-25 belongs to the family of Russian grenade launchers that fit on AK assault rifles. It is muzzle-loaded.

Grenade launcher for Warsaw Pact firearms
Can load and fire VOG-25 grenades
Fits on: AK-74, AKM, AN-94
</name>
</text>

<!--Empty Blood Bag-->
<text>
	<id>109</id>
	<name>An IV set along with a sterile blood bag can be used to draw your own blood for a single use in the future.

Use when health is above 50%
Transfuses blood into a Blood Bag
</name>
</text>

<!--Sharpening Stone-->
<text>
	<id>110</id>
	<name>The whetstone can be used to sharpen the edges of various bladed weapons and tools.

Sharpens weapons
Restores 25% durability to certain melee weapons
</name>
</text>

<!--AK Grip-->
<text>
	<id>111</id>
	<name>A universal tactical forend for AK series weapons.

Greatly reduces recoil when firing
Fits on: AK-74, AKM, RPK
Can be crafted: Laser AK Grip (requires Laser Sight)
</name>
</text>

<!--Rail Grip-->
<text>
	<id>112</id>
	<name>A foregrip for firearms with Picatinny rails.

Greatly reduces recoil when firing
Fits on: UMP-45, M4, L85, Vector
Can be crafted: Laser Rail Grip (requires Laser Sight)
</name>
</text>

<!--Marked Map-->
<text>
	<id>113</id>
	<name>A map with some markings, contains notes about interesting places, checkpoints, POIs and vehicles on the current island.

A marked map revealing hidden locations on the island
Only works on the current island
If not used on this island, will disappear from the inventory on the next island
</name>
</text>

<!--Elderberries-->
<text>
	<id>114</id>
	<name>Elderberries are small, dark purple colored black berries, known for their fragrant creamy flavor and rich nutrients. They grow only in swamps.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +10
Health: +2
Max Stack: 5
</name>
</text>

<!--Binoculars-->
<text>
	<id>115</id>
	<name>A pair of binoculars for scouting distant areas.
</name>
</text>

<!--Scout Handbook-->
<text>
	<id>116</id>
	<name>The scout handbook provides a comprehensive guide for scouting activities, covering areas like camping, survival skills, first aid, and leadership.

Experience: +200
</name>
</text>

<!--Tarpaulin-->
<text>
	<id>117</id>
	<name>Burlap sacks rolled into a roll for later use.

Can be crafted: Supply Cache (requires Wood)
</name>
</text>

<!--Medical Tape-->
<text>
	<id>118</id>
	<name>A type of medical tape with adhesive properties, can be used to directly stop the bleeding in an instant.

Stops bleeding
Use Time: 1 sec
Max Stack: 5
</name>
</text>

<!--Smoke Grenade-->
<text>
	<id>119</id>
	<name>A smoke grenade used by western forces. The smoke is colorless and can provide complete cover against enemies.

Creates a smoke screen for 15 seconds, obscuring enemy vision
</name>
</text>

<!--Cigarettes-->
<text>
	<id>120</id>
	<name>"Russian cigarettes" filled with a high-nicotine, potent tobacco called makhorka and were popular throughout the Soviet era.

Smoking is harmful to health
Temperature: +5
Reputation: +5 when given to survivors
Effect: Slows hunger and thirst rate
Duration: 30 sec
Max Stack: 10
</name>
</text>

<!--Beer-->
<text>
	<id>121</id>
	<name>Beer cans usually last 6-9 months at room temperature. The taste is a little off, but is still refreshingly sweet.

Remember, drinking is harmful, consume in moderation
Thirst: +20
Temperature: +10
</name>
</text>

<!--Epoxy-->
<text>
	<id>122</id>
	<name>Epoxy glue is a strong, two-part adhesive made from epoxy resin and a hardener.

Repairs most equipment by 25% durability
</name>
</text>

<!--Fertilizer-->
<text>
	<id>123</id>
	<name>Composed of plant matter and animal wastes, it is rich in essential nutrients that plants love.

Increases plant growth rate
</name>
</text>

<!--Laser Sight-->
<text>
	<id>124</id>
	<name>Laser sights project a laser beam onto a target, aiding in aiming speed and recoil recovery.

Aim Speed and Recoil Recovery: +30%
Fits on: UMP-45, Vector, AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, M4, L85, RPK, Mosin-Nagant, SKS, SVD, SV-98, VSS, M70, Saiga-12k, Blaze, Mini-14, AS-VAL
Can be crafted: Laser AK Grip (requires AK Grip), Laser Rail Grip (requires Rail Grip)
</name>
</text>

<!--Lighter-->
<text>
	<id>125</id>
	<name>The lighter creates a flame using a mechanical ignition system, powered by a flint and wheel mechanism.

Can light campfire kits or cigarettes
</name>
</text>

<!--Keycard-->
<text>
	<id>126</id>
	<name>An officer's keycard. A critical key for managing access to sensitive areas, authorized gear and maintaining security within a military facility.

A keycard of unknown origin, opens special bunker doors
Only works on bunkers on the current island
</name>
</text>

<!--Makeshift Suppressor-->
<text>
	<id>127</id>
	<name>A homemade DIY suppressor that can reduce some firearm noise. It just works.

A makeshift homemade suppressor, slightly reduces weapon noise
Fits on: M4, M16A2, L85, AUG, FN-FAL, AKs-74u, AN-94, Ak-74, AKM, FAMAS, Mini-14, M249
</name>
</text>

<!--PVS-4 Night Vision Scope-->
<text>
	<id>128</id>
	<name>A standardized rail-mounted 3.5x magnifier with night vision, made for NATO firearms.

A standardized rail-mounted night vision scope
Spread: -2
Headshot Chance: +12%
Aiming Distance: +10%
Night Vision: +10%
Fits on: MP5, UMP-45, Vector, M4, M16A2, L85, FN-FAL, SV-98, Mini-14, AS-VAL, M249
</name>
</text>

<!--1PN51 Night Vision Scope-->
<text>
	<id>129</id>
	<name>A side-mounted 3.5x magnifier with night vision, suitable for Warsaw Pact firearms.

A side-mounted night vision scope
Spread: -2
Headshot Chance: +12%
Aiming Distance: +10%
Night Vision: +10%
Fits on: AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, RPK, Bizon, Groza, VSS, Saiga-12k
</name>
</text>

<!--C-MAG 5.56-->
<text>
	<id>130</id>
	<name>A 100-round 5.56x45 dual drum magazine.

Dual 100-round drum magazine for 5.56×45
Fits on: M4, M16A2, AUG
</name>
</text>

<!--7.62x39 Drum Mag-->
<text>
	<id>131</id>
	<name>A 75-round 7.62x39 drum magazine.

75-round drum magazine for 7.62×39
Fits on: AKM, RPK
</name>
</text>

<!--Frying Pan-->
<text>
	<id>132</id>
	<name>Bon Appétit.

Can bullets even penetrate this?
Damage: 25-41
Crit Chance: 40%
Block Chance: 35%
Attack Speed: 0.9s
Can Cook: Fried Egg (requires Egg + Campfire), Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes (requires Egg + Tomato + Campfire), Pepper Steak (requires Raw Steak/Raw Rabbit/Raw Chicken + Bell Pepper + Campfire)
</name>
</text>

<!--Gas Mask-->
<text>
	<id>133</id>
	<name>A form of personal protective equipment (PPE) that protects the wearer from inhaling airborne pollutants and toxic gases.

Uses durability to filter contaminated air
Heat: +2
Provides immunity against toxic gas contaminated areas; durability wears constantly in contaminated areas
Can be worn as a liner to wear other headgear on top of it
Click the empty head slot to unequip it when used as a liner
</name>
</text>

<!--Balaclava-->
<text>
	<id>134</id>
	<name>A close-fitting head covering that protects the head, face and neck, leaving only the eyes or parts of the face exposed.

Heat: +2
Can be worn as a liner to wear other headgear on top of it
Click the empty head slot to unequip it when used as a liner
</name>
</text>

<!--GP-5 Gas Mask-->
<text>
	<id>135</id>
	<name>A full-face Soviet gas mask with a frontal mount for filter cartridges. Used to protect from airborne pollutants and contaminated air.

Heat: +1
Uses durability to filter contaminated air
Provides immunity against toxic gas; has more durability but wears constantly in contaminated areas
Can be worn as a liner to wear other headgear on top of it
Click the empty head slot to unequip it when used as a liner
</name>
</text>

<!--Clown Mask-->
<text>
	<id>136</id>
	<name>The headgear of choice of the clowning around degenerate island thugs.

When worn, killing neutral survivors or merchants does not reduce reputation
Heat: +1
Can be worn as a liner to wear other headgear on top of it
Click the empty head slot to unequip it when used as a liner
</name>
</text>

<!--Dog Gear-->
<text>
	<id>137</id>
	<name>Originally designed for military use, its good quality quickly brought it to the civilian market.

Melee Block Chance: +5%
When worn, looting zombies has no penalty
</name>
</text>

<!--.308 Ammo-->
<text>
	<id>138</id>
	<name>.308 Winchester full-power cartridge. Used in select rifles.

Chambered in: M70, FN-FAL, Blaze, Sawn-off Blaze, Longhorn
Max Stack: 40
</name>
</text>

<!--Sneakers-->
<text>
	<id>139</id>
	<name>A pair of ordinary sneakers.

Standard athletic shoes
Movement Speed: +5%
May be damaged by stepping in acid
</name>
</text>

<!--Woodland Boots-->
<text>
	<id>140</id>
	<name>Woodland boots designed for wet environments.

Combat boots designed for wet environments
Movement Speed: +5%, ignores swamp slowdown
May be damaged by stepping in acid
</name>
</text>

<!--Assault Boots-->
<text>
	<id>141</id>
	<name>Designed for soldiers in combat.

Movement Speed: +10%, ignores swamp slowdown
Allows holstering a knife
May be damaged by stepping in acid
</name>
</text>

<!--Rifle Sling-->
<text>
	<id>142</id>
	<name>Can be attached as a shoulder accessory to carry an additional primary weapon on your back.

Allows you to holster an additional firearm on your back
Click the empty weapon slot to unequip
</name>
</text>

<!--Charcoal Tablets-->
<text>
	<id>143</id>
	<name>Activated charcoal tablets that can filter out toxins.

Restores 50% durability to gas masks
</name>
</text>

<!--Blowtorch-->
<text>
	<id>144</id>
	<name>Can weld 25% durability of vehicles or metallic equipment.

Repairs vehicles or metal equipment by 25% durability
Can reinforce vehicles with metal plates, making them immune to collision damage
</name>
</text>

<!--Ghillie Suit-->
<text>
	<id>145</id>
	<name>A camouflage suit used to completely conceal the wearer in a natural environment.

Activates when durability is above 50%. Grants invisibility when standing still for a short time.
Moving or attacking breaks invisibility. Invisible targets cannot be seen.
</name>
</text>

<!--Underbarrel Flashlight-->
<text>
	<id>146</id>
	<name>A mounted underbarrel flashlight for primary weapons, providing illumination at night.

Attaches to firearms or assault helmets, providing a small cone of light at night
Fits on: UMP-45, Vector, AKs-74u, Ak-74, AN-94, AKM, M4, L85, RPK, Mosin-Nagant, SKS, SVD, SV-98, VSS, M70, Saiga-12k, Blaze, Mini-14, AS-VAL
</name>
</text>

<!--Laser AK Grip-->
<text>
	<id>147</id>
	<name>A universal front grip and side-mounted laser sight for AK series firearms.
Greatly reduces recoil when firing
Aim Speed and Recoil Recovery: +30%

Universal foregrip with side-mounted laser for AK series rifles
Fits on: AK-74, AKM, RPK
</name>
</text>

<!--Laser Rail Grip-->
<text>
	<id>148</id>
	<name>A foregrip and laser sight for firearms with Picatinny rails.
Greatly reduces recoil when firing
Aim Speed and Recoil Recovery: +30%

Foregrip with laser sight for Picatinny rail-equipped firearms
Fits on: UMP-45, Vector, M4, L85
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pistols-->
<!-- fnx -->
<text>
	<id>211</id>
	<name>A nimble pistol favored by many.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 21-35             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 9
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 15
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- colt -->
<text>
	<id>212</id>
	<name>"God created men, Colt made them equal."
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 7
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- magnum -->
<text>
	<id>213</id>
	<name>One of the most powerful handguns in the world.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 34-56             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 15
Run Penalty: 3              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 6
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- glock -->
<text>
	<id>214</id>
	<name>A semi-automatic pistol made in Austria.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 15-25             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9mm
Mag Capacity: 18
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- amphibia-->
<text>
	<id>215</id>
	<name>A pistol designed for underwater combat by naval personnel.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 11-19             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 9
Run Penalty: 3              Ammo: .22 LR
Mag Capacity: 10
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- IZH S-->
<text>
	<id>216</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the IZH-43 shotgun.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 13
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 12 Gauge
Mag Capacity: 2
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Mosin S-->
<text>
	<id>217</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the Mosin-Nagant rifle.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 12
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 25
Run Penalty: 1              Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Mag Capacity: 5
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Rare colt-->
<text>
	<id>218</id>
	<name>A meticulously engraved Colt pistol.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 12
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Mac-->
<text>
	<id>219</id>
	<name>One of the world-famous firearms made in the USA.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 15-25             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 9mm
Fire Rate: 650 RPM
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Rossi-->
<text>
	<id>220</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the Rossi M92 lever-action rifle.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 34-56             Spread: 11
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 17
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 7
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- PM-->
<text>
	<id>221</id>
	<name>Small, lightweight, favored by Soviet officers.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9x18mm
Mag Capacity: 8
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- PB-->
<text>
	<id>222</id>
	<name>A Soviet integrally suppressed, semi-automatic pistol developed for covert special operations by the KGB and Spetsnaz.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 9
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 8
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9x18mm
Mag Capacity: 8
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Deagle-->
<text>
	<id>223</id>
	<name>A favorite among firearm collectors.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 13
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 9
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- M79-->
<text>
	<id>224</id>
	<name>It might look outdated, but it's still effective.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 45-540           Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 40mm Grenade
Mag Capacity: 1
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Blaze S-->
<text>
	<id>225</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the Blaze double-barreled rifle.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 71-119           Spread: 12
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .308
Mag Capacity: 2
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Longhorn -->
<text>
	<id>226</id>
	<name>Can only hold one round, but its integrated scope provides exceptional accuracy.
Integrated Scope
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 1
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 25
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .308
Mag Capacity: 1
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Mini-UZI-->
<text>
	<id>227</id>
	<name>A lightweight submachine gun manufactured in Israel.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 22          Ammo: .45 ACP
Fire Rate: 600 RPM
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Main Weapons-->

<!-- Mosin-Nagant-->
<text>
	<id>232</id>
	<name>A rifle produced in Russia in the late 19th century.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 5              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 5           Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Fire Rate: 46 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M4-->
<text>
	<id>233</id>
	<name>A reliable rifle used by the US military.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-38             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- IZH-43-->
<text>
	<id>234</id>
	<name>A hunter's best friend.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 13
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 2           Ammo: 12 Gauge
Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AK-74-->
<text>
	<id>235</id>
	<name>A Soviet-made rifle built for harsh environments.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 26-44             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.45x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AKM-->
<text>
	<id>236</id>
	<name>A firearm derived from a legendary weapon.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 5
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 7.62x39mm
Fire Rate: 460 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AK-74u-->
<text>
	<id>237</id>
	<name>One of the standard issue weapons of the Russian Army.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 26-44             Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 1              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.45x39mm
Fire Rate: 750 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- SKS-->
<text>
	<id>238</id>
	<name>A reliable weapon manufactured in the Soviet Union.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 34-56             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 4              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 10          Ammo: 7.62x39mm
Fire Rate: 200 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- L85-->
<text>
	<id>240</id>
	<name>One of the main weapons of the British military.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-38             Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 500 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Remington-->
<text>
	<id>241</id>
	<name>A popular weapon favored by American civilians.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 15
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 6           Ammo: 12 Gauge
Fire Rate: 66 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Bow-->
<text>
	<id>243</id>
	<name>A weapon from thousands of years ago, still in use today.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 37-94             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 2               Run Penalty: 3
Ammo: Handmade Arrow / Composite Arrow
Mag Capacity: 1            Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- CrossBow-->
<text>
	<id>244</id>
	<name>A crossbow, terrifyingly effective.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 37-94             Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 2               Run Penalty: 3
Ammo: Handmade Arrow / Composite Arrow
Mag Capacity: 1            Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sporter-->
<text>
	<id>246</id>
	<name>A small-caliber rifle.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 15-25             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 8
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: .22 LR
Fire Rate: 300 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Repeater-->
<text>
	<id>247</id>
	<name>A military weapon used by the British in the late 19th century.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 7           Ammo: .357
Fire Rate: 85 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- SVD-->
<text>
	<id>248</id>
	<name>A Soviet sniper rifle that replaced the Mosin-Nagant.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 71-119           Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 13
Run Penalty: 5              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 10          Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Fire Rate: 150 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- MP5k-->
<text>
	<id>249</id>
	<name>An ultra-compact submachine gun made in Germany.
Integrated Grip
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 21-35             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 1
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 9mm
Fire Rate: 850 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- UMP-->
<text>
	<id>251</id>
	<name>A personal defense weapon used by US special forces.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 21-35             Spread: 9
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: .45 ACP
Fire Rate: 650 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- RPK-->
<text>
	<id>252</id>
	<name>A light machine gun derived from the AKM.
Integrated Bipod: Significantly reduces recoil after standing still.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 40          Ammo: 7.62x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- FN-FAL-->
<text>
	<id>253</id>
	<name>A battle rifle developed in Belgium.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 54-90             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 20          Ammo: .308
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Saiga-12k-->
<text>
	<id>254</id>
	<name>A semi-automatic combat shotgun made in Russia.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 17
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 19
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 8           Ammo: 12 Gauge
Fire Rate: 200 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AUG-->
<text>
	<id>255</id>
	<name>The first mass-produced bullpup rifle with a modular design.
Integrated Scope and Grip: Headshot Chance +15%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 25-41             Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 1.5
Run Penalty: 2.5           Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 650 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Bizon-->
<text>
	<id>256</id>
	<name>A uniquely designed submachine gun made in Russia.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 64          Ammo: 9x18mm
Fire Rate: 550 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Groza-->
<text>
	<id>257</id>
	<name>Russian assault rifle with an integrated grenade launcher system.
Integrated GP-25 Grenade Launcher
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 9x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- VSS-->
<text>
	<id>258</id>
	<name>A silenced sniper rifle manufactured in the Soviet Union.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 37-62             Spread: 2
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 20          Ammo: 9x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- SV-98-->
<text>
	<id>259</id>
	<name>A sniper rifle optimized from the SVD platform.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 86-144           Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 9
Run Penalty: 5              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 10          Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Fire Rate: 66 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
+10% Headshot chance at precise aim
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Madsen-->
<text>
	<id>260</id>
	<name>The world's first true LMG, adopted by the Royal Danish Army in 1902.
Integrated Bipod: Significantly reduces recoil after standing still.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 52-87             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Fire Rate: 500 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AN-94-->
<text>
	<id>261</id>
	<name>A complex Russian-made assault rifle, its most distinctive feature is the "hyper burst" firing 2 shots at the same time.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 28-46             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.45x39mm
Fire Rate: 1800 RPM       Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Silenced Remington-->
<text>
	<id>262</id>
	<name>"When you try to reclaim what you've lost, you might lose even more..."
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 15
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 6           Ammo: 12 Gauge
Fire Rate: 66 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M16A2-->
<text>
	<id>263</id>
	<name>One of the rifles in the US standard-issue M16 series.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-38             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 800 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Vector-->
<text>
	<id>264</id>
	<name>Exceptional stability and a blistering fire rate make this weapon terrifying.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 21-35             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: .45 ACP
Fire Rate: 1200 RPM       Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M4 w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>265</id>
	<name>A reliable rifle used by the US military. Currently fitted with a C-Mag Drum.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-38             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 100         Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AKM w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>266</id>
	<name>A firearm derived from a legendary weapon. Currently fitted with a Drum Mag.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 5
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 75          Ammo: 7.62x39mm
Fire Rate: 460 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M70-->
<text>
	<id>267</id>
	<name>The Winchester Model 70 is a bolt-action target rifle extensively used in the Vietnam war.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 5              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 5           Ammo: .308
Fire Rate: 46 RPM         Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Saiga-12k w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>268</id>
	<name>A semi-automatic combat shotgun made in Russia. Currently fitted with a Drum Mag.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 17
Aim Speed: 1               Recoil: 19
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 20          Ammo: 12 Gauge
Fire Rate: 200 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- RPK w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>269</id>
	<name>A light machine gun derived from the AKM. Currently fitted with a Drum Mag.
Integrated Bipod: Significantly reduces recoil after standing still.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 75          Ammo: 7.62x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M16A2 w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>270</id>
	<name>One of the rifles in the US standard-issue M16 series. Currently fitted with a C-Mag Drum.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-38             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 100         Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 800 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AUG w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>271</id>
	<name>The first mass-produced bullpup rifle with a modular design. Currently fitted with a C-Mag Drum.
Integrated Scope and Grip: Headshot Chance +15%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 25-41             Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 1.5
Run Penalty: 2.5           Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 100         Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 650 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- MGL-->
<text>
	<id>272</id>
	<name>A lightweight 40mm six-shot revolver grenade launcher.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 45-540           Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 2.5           Reload Time: 4s
Mag Capacity: 6           Ammo: 40mm Grenade
Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Blaze-->
<text>
	<id>273</id>
	<name>A break-action hunting rifle, favored for its unique ability to fire two rounds almost instantly.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 71-119           Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 2           Ammo: .308
Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- FAMAS-->
<text>
	<id>274</id>
	<name>A bullpup assault rifle designed for compactness and a high fire rate.
Integrated Bipod: Significantly reduces recoil after standing still.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 25-41             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 25          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 900 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Mini-14-->
<text>
	<id>275</id>
	<name>The Ruger Mini-14 is a lightweight, semi-automatic rifle, valued for its classic design, reliability, and versatility.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 27-45             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 3
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 20          Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 300 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AK-74 w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>276</id>
	<name>A Soviet-made rifle built for harsh environments. Currently fitted with a C-Mag Drum.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 26-44             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 95          Ammo: 5.45x39mm
Fire Rate: 600 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AK-74u w/ Drum-->
<text>
	<id>277</id>
	<name>One of the standard issue weapons of the Russian Army. Currently fitted with a C-Mag Drum.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 26-44             Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 1              Reload Time: 3s
Mag Capacity: 95          Ammo: 5.45x39mm
Fire Rate: 750 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- AS-VAL-->
<text>
	<id>278</id>
	<name>A derivative of the VSS, featuring a Picatinny rail on the receiver.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 37-62             Spread: 3
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 2              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 9x39mm
Fire Rate: 800 RPM        Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M249-->
<text>
	<id>279</id>
	<name>An American light machine gun, using 100-round belt-fed ammunition boxes. Highly reliable and offers tremendous firepower.
Integrated Bipod: Significantly reduces recoil after standing still.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 25-41             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 1.5             Recoil: 4
Run Penalty: 3              Reload Time: 4s
Mag Capacity: 100         Ammo: 5.56x45mm
Fire Rate: 1000 RPM       Wear per Shot: 0.2%
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Backpacks -->
<!-- Taloon-->
<text>
	<id>301</id>
	<name>A lightweight backpack used for all-day trips. Comfortably supports any load that fits in.

Carry Capacity: +5
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>302</id>
	<name>A tall mountaineering backpack made from hi-tech materials. Spacious but very noticeable.

Carry Capacity: +11
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>303</id>
	<name>A standard hunting backpack with closable pockets. Very durable and comfortable, if a little old-fashioned.

Carry Capacity: +7
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>304</id>
	<name>A child's backpack. Not very practical in terms of carrying space, but helps keep a low profile.

Carry Capacity: +3
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>305</id>
	<name>A small, low-profile bag suspended by one strap over the shoulder. This bag won't fit that much inside, but it's very discreet and won't be noticed as easily.

Carry Capacity: +4
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>306</id>
	<name>A low-profile burlap backpack with a wooden frame. Not too rigid, but very practical.

Carry Capacity: +6
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>307</id>
	<name>A civilian camping tent combo with a backpack. Offers a comfortable and dry space when deployed, with additional storage space for your loot.

Can be placed on the ground
Items stored inside will never disappear
Carry Capacity: +3
Can store spare top-wear and pants
Can be deployed on the ground as a civilian tent to store items
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>308</id>
	<name>A comfortable military backpack for prolonged carrying. Hits the sweet spot in carrying a lot more gear while still being minimal in size.

Carry Capacity: +9
Can store spare top-wear and pants
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>309</id>
	<name>A handy fanny pack used to carry small items. The material isn't very durable, but it will do the job.

Carry Capacity: +2
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>310</id>
	<name>A small army-grade shoulder bag used to store small EDC survival items and tools.

Carry Capacity: +1
Utility Slots: +3
Can store knives, matches, lighters, flares, canteens
Can be worn on the chest, along with a backpack
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>311</id>
	<name>A medical-grade IFAK shoulder bag, designed to store medicine in a protected manner against contaminants.

Carry Capacity: +1
Medical Slots: +3
Can store any medical supplies, any medicine
Can be worn on the chest, along with a backpack
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>312</id>
	<name>A touch of the Devs' magic to give your items the ability to dimension jump!

Carry Capacity: +6
Items stored inside can be carried over to the next game
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pants -->
<!-- Jeans-->
<text>
	<id>351</id>
	<name>Denim trousers, also known as jeans. Omnipresent casual modern clothing, these are your average pants.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Worker-->
<text>
	<id>352</id>
	<name>Loosely cut pants suitable for tough work in the outdoors. Distinguishable by pockets on legs.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sport-->
<text>
	<id>353</id>
	<name>Casual pants, designed for comfort and athletic purposes. They have become one of the most commonly worn items of clothing in the world.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +3
</name>
</text>

<!-- Gorka-->
<text>
	<id>354</id>
	<name>Tactical pants used by the unit stationed at Gorka. They offer quick access to large cargo pockets, armor, and decent protection from the elements.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +8
Defense: +2
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Medic-->
<text>
	<id>355</id>
	<name>Standard issue paramedic pants. Not that different from any other work apparel, except for the bright, reflective stripes.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +4
</name>
</text>

<!-- Orel-->
<text>
	<id>356</id>
	<name>Uniform pants of the OREL special police force unit. Somewhat warm and comfortable with little protection.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
Defense: +1
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hunter-->
<text>
	<id>357</id>
	<name>Durable pants, designed for prolonged periods of time spent outdoors. The camo pattern makes for an ideal hunting outfit in the right environment.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +6
Defense: +1
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Firefighter Pants-->
<text>
	<id>358</id>
	<name>Flame-resistant pants designed for firefighters. Offers protection against high temperatures.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
Defense: +1
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Provides fire protection (requires Firefighter Jacket to be equipped simultaneously)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Vests -->
<!-- Bulletproof-->
<text>
	<id>401</id>
	<name>A fabric shell covered over a ballistic armor plate. Good cover protection for the front of the torso.

Defense: +8
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- assault-->
<text>
	<id>402</id>
	<name>A tactical vest designed for combat, which prioritizes carrying gear and ammunition. Offers limited protection from soft padding.

Carry Capacity: +2
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Can attach grenades and smoke grenades, up to 3
</name>
</text>

<!-- press-->
<text>
	<id>403</id>
	<name>A ballistic press vest able to absorb various types of impact damage. Used by various security organizations around the world.

Carry Capacity: +1
Defense: +6
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- High Capacity-->
<text>
	<id>404</id>
	<name>A tactical vest designed to hold as much gear as possible while maintaining full mobility. Offers limited protection from soft padding.

Carry Capacity: +3
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Can attach grenades and smoke grenades, up to 3
</name>
</text>

<!-- Kevlar-->
<text>
	<id>405</id>
	<name>A type of hard body armor made from the strong, synthetic material Kevlar. Highly effective at stopping rounds while maintaining a balance between mobility and carry capacity.

Carry Capacity: +3
Defense: +10
Melee Block Chance: +10%
Can attach grenades and smoke grenades, up to 3
</name>
</text>

<!-- Soviet-->
<text>
	<id>406</id>
	<name>Soviet forces edition. A dedicated tactical vest that offers greater protection to the lower abdomen due to an elongated chest section.

Carry Capacity: +2
Defense: +8
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Apron-->
<text>
	<id>407</id>
	<name>A versatile garment worn over clothes to protect the wearer's body and clothing from substances like dirt, guts, grease, and chemicals.

Carry Capacity: +1
</name>
</text>

<!-- Ghillie Suit (Vest)-->
<text>
	<id>408</id>
	<name>A camouflage suit used to completely conceal the wearer in a natural environment.

Activates when durability is above 50%. Grants invisibility when standing still for a short time.
Moving or attacking breaks invisibility. Invisible targets cannot be seen.
</name>
</text>

<!-- M Heavy Armor-->
<text>
	<id>409</id>
	<name>Top-grade military armor coated with a layer of experimental compound called "Complex M". Stops rounds like its nothing.

Defense: +20
Melee Block Chance: +15%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class A Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>410</id>
	<name>An airtight Class A Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be sealed to block contaminated air for 2 minutes (requires full protection).
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Thermal Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>411</id>
	<name>A kevlar vest layered on top of a CBRN suit.

Carry Capacity: +3
Defense: +10
Melee Block Chance: +10%
Can attach grenades and smoke grenades, up to 3
Contains the properties of a CBRN suit
</name>
</text>

<!-- Military M Heavy Suit-->
<text>
	<id>412</id>
	<name>An M heavy armor layered on top of a CBRN suit.

Defense: +20
Melee Block Chance: +15%
Contains the properties of a CBRN suit
</name>
</text>

<!-- Military Ghillie Suit-->
<text>
	<id>413</id>
	<name>A ghillie suit layered on top of a CBRN suit.

Activates when durability is above 50%. Grants invisibility when standing still for a short time.
Moving or attacking breaks invisibility.
Contains the properties of a CBRN suit
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class C Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>414</id>
	<name>A basic protection Class C Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class B Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>415</id>
	<name>A radiation-proof Class B Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class A Military Suit-->
<text>
	<id>416</id>
	<name>A military-grade protective suit, allows attachment of Ghillie suit, Kevlar vest, and M Heavy Armor.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be sealed to block contaminated air for 2 minutes (requires full protection).
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Helmets -->
<text>
	<id>450</id>
	<name>Click to remove the attached equipment
</name>
</text>

<!-- Motorcycle Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>451</id>
	<name>A protective helmet with a visor for motorcycle riders. The hard outer shell absorbs impacts with ease.

Heat: +2
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Army Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>452</id>
	<name>An army infantry helmet, a piece of ballistic headgear designed for protection against fragmentation, blunt impact, and some small firearms.

Heat: +2
Defense: +4
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Reduces headshot damage
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hard Hat-->
<text>
	<id>453</id>
	<name>A construction helmet used to protect the head from the impact of falling tools, debris, or any blunt force.

Heat: +2
Defense: +2
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Gas Mask-->
<text>
	<id>454</id>
	<name>A form of personal protective equipment that protects the wearer from inhaling airborne pollutants and toxic gases.

Heat: +2
Provides immunity against toxic gas; durability decreases in contaminated areas
Can be worn as a liner under other headgear
</name>
</text>

<!-- Motorcycle Helmet 2-->
<text>
	<id>455</id>
	<name>A protective helmet with a visor for motorcycle riders. The hard outer shell absorbs impacts with ease.

Heat: +2
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Motorcycle Helmet 3-->
<text>
	<id>456</id>
	<name>A protective helmet with a visor for motorcycle riders. The hard outer shell absorbs impacts with ease.

Heat: +2
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Cap-->
<text>
	<id>457</id>
	<name>A soft cap with a curved bill and rounded crown. It is effective at shielding the eyes from the sun.

Heat: +2
</name>
</text>

<!-- Warm Hat-->
<text>
	<id>458</id>
	<name>A soft, close-fitting brimless beanie that is known for its versatility and warmth.

Heat: +4
</name>
</text>

<!-- Ushanka-->
<text>
	<id>459</id>
	<name>A traditional Russian fur hat with ear flaps that can be tied in different positions to provide maximum protection from extreme cold.

Heat: +6
</name>
</text>

<!-- Beret-->
<text>
	<id>460</id>
	<name>A beret with an insignia stitched on one side. It doesn't offer much protection, nor does it provide much thermal comfort.

Heat: +2
</name>
</text>

<!-- Balaclava-->
<text>
	<id>461</id>
	<name>A close-fitting head covering that protects the head, face, and neck, leaving only the eyes or parts of the face exposed.

Heat: +3
Can be worn as a liner under other headgear
</name>
</text>

<!-- Headlamp-->
<text>
	<id>462</id>
	<name>A hands-free lighting device worn on the head with an adjustable strap.

Heat: +1
Requires a battery to operate
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Cowboy Hat-->
<text>
	<id>463</id>
	<name>A high-crowned, wide-brimmed cowboy hat. Associated with ranch workers, cowboys, and men with no names.

Heat: +2
</name>
</text>

<!-- Welding Mask-->
<text>
	<id>464</id>
	<name>Protects the eyes, face, and neck from ultraviolet light, sparks, and heat while welding.

Heat: +1
Defense: +1
</name>
</text>

<!-- Gorka Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>465</id>
	<name>A rugged military helmet designed for harsh weather conditions.

Heat: +3
Defense: +5
Melee Block Chance: +10%
Reduces headshot damage
</name>
</text>

<!-- Police Cap-->
<text>
	<id>466</id>
	<name>A peaked police cap is worn as part of a police uniform.

Heat: +2
</name>
</text>

<!-- NVG-->
<text>
	<id>467</id>
	<name>Battery-powered Night Vision Goggles for intensifying images in low-light environments. Comes with a headstrap.

Heat: +1
Requires a battery to operate
Can be placed in inventory slots.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Bandana-->
<text>
	<id>468</id>
	<name>A piece of cloth worn around the head. Typically made of cotton or silk, bandanas are versatile and can be styled in many ways.

Heat: +2
Can be torn into rags
</name>
</text>

<!-- Crusader Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>469</id>
	<name>A full-face helm made of cold steel, designed to offer superior head protection during the brutal melee of medieval warfare.

Heat: +4
Defense: +5
Melee Block Chance: +15%
Reduces headshot damage
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pilot Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>470</id>
	<name>A helmet designed to provide protection to pilots, along with electronic wiring throughout to allow microphone communication. Comes with a protective visor.

Heat: +3
Defense: +2
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Altyn Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>471</id>
	<name>A 4mm thick layer of stamped titanium shell helmet equipped with a face shield. Stops rounds like its nothing.

Heat: +3
Defense: +7
Melee Block Chance: +10%
Reduces headshot damage
</name>
</text>

<!-- "Killa" Altyn Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>472</id>
	<name>A 4mm thick layer of stamped titanium shell helmet equipped with a face shield. Stops rounds like its nothing. It's also spray-painted to resemble a "Killa Helmet".

Heat: +3
Defense: +7
Melee Block Chance: +10%
Reduces headshot damage
</name>
</text>

<!-- GP-5 Gas Mask-->
<text>
	<id>473</id>
	<name>A full-face Soviet gas mask with a frontal mount for filter cartridges. Used to protect from airborne pollutants and contaminated air.

Heat: +2
Provides immunity against toxic gas; has more durability but wears constantly in contaminated areas
Can be worn as a liner under other headgear
</name>
</text>

<!-- Clown Mask-->
<text>
	<id>474</id>
	<name>The headgear of choice for the clowning around, degenerate island thugs.

Heat: +1
Can be worn as a liner under other headgear
</name>
</text>

<!-- Assault Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>475</id>
	<name>A ballistic helmet with rails for accessories and an NVG shroud. Designed to meet combat applications in the dark while protecting the head.

Heat: +3
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Reduces headshot damage
Can mount night vision and flashlight attachments
</name>
</text>

<!-- Assault Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>476</id>
	<name>A ballistic helmet with rails for accessories and an NVG shroud. Designed to meet combat applications in the dark while protecting the head.

Heat: +3
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Reduces headshot damage
Can mount night vision and flashlight attachments
</name>
</text>

<!-- Assault Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>477</id>
	<name>A ballistic helmet with rails for accessories and an NVG shroud. Designed to meet combat applications in the dark while protecting the head.

Heat: +3
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Reduces headshot damage
Can mount night vision and flashlight attachments
</name>
</text>

<!-- Assault Helmet-->
<text>
	<id>478</id>
	<name>A ballistic helmet with rails for accessories and an NVG shroud. Designed to meet combat applications in the dark while protecting the head.

Heat: +3
Defense: +3
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Reduces headshot damage
Can mount night vision and flashlight attachments
</name>
</text>

<!-- Outfits -->
<!-- Hoodie-->
<text>
	<id>501</id>
	<name>A hooded sweatshirt with a vertical zipper and two large pockets. Provides decent protection from the elements.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Shirt-->
<text>
	<id>502</id>
	<name>A common long-sleeved, button-up, cloth garment for the upper body made from polyester and cotton.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +3
Can be torn into rags
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hoodie-->
<text>
	<id>504</id>
	<name>A hooded sweatshirt with a vertical zipper and two large pockets. Provides decent protection from the elements.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Raincoat-->
<text>
	<id>505</id>
	<name>A jacket made from water-resistant fabric with an extended collar and hood. Helps protect the upper body from rain.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +6
Rainproof, unaffected by rain
</name>
</text>

<!-- Raincoat-->
<text>
	<id>506</id>
	<name>A jacket made from water-resistant fabric with an extended collar and hood. Helps protect the upper body from rain.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +6
Rainproof, unaffected by rain
</name>
</text>

<!-- Raider Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>507</id>
	<name>A classic motorcycle leather jacket. Rugged, durable, and protective. Not to mention badass.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +4
Defense: +2
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Fur Coat-->
<text>
	<id>509</id>
	<name>A long, loose fur coat with a belt, usually made from insulated material and similar in style to a military coat.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +9
</name>
</text>

<!-- Gorka Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>510</id>
	<name>A tactical jacket used by the unit stationed at Gorka. Offers quick access to large cargo pockets, armor, and decent protection from the elements.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +8
Defense: +2
Melee Block Chance: +10%
</name>
</text>

<!-- T-Shirt-->
<text>
	<id>511</id>
	<name>A short-sleeve T-shirt with a round neckline and a regular fit. Nothing special.

Can be torn into rags
</name>
</text>

<!-- Paramedic Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>512</id>
	<name>A standard issue paramedic jacket. Not that different from any other work apparel, except for the bright, reflective stripes.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Orel Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>513</id>
	<name>The uniform jacket of the OREL special police force unit. Somewhat warm, comfortable, and armored.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
Defense: +1
</name>
</text>

<!-- Tracksuit Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>514</id>
	<name>A casual jacket, designed for comfort and athletic purposes. It has become one of the most commonly worn items of clothing in the world.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +4
</name>
</text>

<!-- Dress-->
<text>
	<id>515</id>
	<name>A comfortable women's dress. Will keep you looking pretty in any situation.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +4
</name>
</text>

<!-- Down Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>516</id>
	<name>A highly compressible puffer jacket filled with soft, warm under-feathers from ducks or geese. Feels cozy.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +8
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hunter Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>517</id>
	<name>A durable jacket, designed for prolonged periods of time spent outdoors. The camo pattern makes for an ideal hunting outfit in the right environment.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +6
Defense: +1
Melee Block Chance: +5%
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sweater-->
<text>
	<id>518</id>
	<name>A thick long-sleeved wool sweater. It is very warm, very absorbent, and itchy as hell.

Carry Capacity: +1
Heat: +6
</name>
</text>

<!-- Awesome Hoodie-->
<text>
	<id>519</id>
	<name>The legendary hoodie of the man, the myth, the legend... Cannedbits AKA Michael Azovsky.

Carry Capacity: +3
Heat: +8
</name>
</text>

<!-- Firefighter Jacket-->
<text>
	<id>520</id>
	<name>A flame-resistant jacket designed for firefighters. Offers protection against high temperatures.

Carry Capacity: +2
Heat: +5
Defense: +1
Melee Block Chance: +5%
Provides fire protection (requires Firefighter Pants to be equipped simultaneously)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Melee -->
<!-- Hands-->
<text>
	<id>550</id>
	<name>When empty-handed, click to retrieve placed bear traps, wire fences, claymores, item stashes, generators, and searchlights.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hatchet-->
<text>
	<id>551</id>
	<name>A single-handed bladed tool with a hammer head on one side. It's the tool for any outdoorsman.

Damage: 38-63
Crit Chance: 25%
Block Chance: 25%
Attack Speed: 1.5s
Can chop trees
</name>
</text>

<!-- Shovel-->
<text>
	<id>552</id>
	<name>An ordinary shovel. The strong, steel blade easily splits both soil and skulls.

Damage: 19-31
Crit Chance: 15%
Block Chance: 35%
Attack Speed: 1.6s
Can be used as a farming tool
Can bury survivor bodies
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pipe Wrench-->
<text>
	<id>553</id>
	<name>An adjustable wrench. Once used for turning nuts or bolts, now it makes a decent blunt weapon.

Damage: 23-38
Crit Chance: 25%
Block Chance: 15%
Attack Speed: 1.3s
Can dismantle structures and salvage metal plates
</name>
</text>

<!-- Baseball Bat-->
<text>
	<id>554</id>
	<name>A wooden baseball bat made for hitting baseballs... or for making an iconic zombie apocalypse weapon for knocking skulls in.

Damage: 26-44
Crit Chance: 25%
Block Chance: 15%
Attack Speed: 1s
Can be crafted: Barbed Wire Baseball Bat (requires Barbed Wire)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Fire Axe-->
<text>
	<id>555</id>
	<name>A firefighter's axe, used primarily for breaking down doors and windows. It's the answer, if the question is a town full of zombies.

Damage: 45-75
Crit Chance: 25%
Block Chance: 25%
Attack Speed: 1.6s
Can chop trees
Can dismantle structures and salvage metal plates
</name>
</text>

<!-- Crowbar-->
<text>
	<id>556</id>
	<name>A durable, multi-purpose melee weapon and tool for prying open doors and crates.

Damage: 19-31
Crit Chance: 25%
Block Chance: 15%
Attack Speed: 1.2s
Can dismantle structures and salvage metal plates
</name>
</text>

<!-- Kitchen Knife-->
<text>
	<id>557</id>
	<name>A standard kitchen knife, sharp enough for most tasks.

Damage: 14-24
Crit Chance: 10%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!-- Hunting Knife-->
<text>
	<id>558</id>
	<name>The hunting knife is a specialized tool designed with a slightly curved tip, primarily for field dressing game.

Damage: 15-25
Crit Chance: 15%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!-- Army Knife-->
<text>
	<id>559</id>
	<name>A sharp combat knife with a sturdy blade and handle. Great for self-defense, but it has other, more mundane uses as well.

Damage: 16-26
Crit Chance: 20%
Block Chance: 5%
Attack Speed: 0.8s
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pickaxe-->
<text>
	<id>560</id>
	<name>An iron pickaxe!...can mine diamonds!...oops, wrong game.

Damage: 33-55
Crit Chance: 15%
Block Chance: 35%
Attack Speed: 1.3s
Can be used as a farming tool
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pitchfork-->
<text>
	<id>561</id>
	<name>An agricultural tool composed of a long handle and thick prongs at one end, used to lift and pitch hay, straw, or leaves, but quite capable of piercing through flesh too.

Damage: 30-50
Crit Chance: 15%
Block Chance: 35%
Attack Speed: 1.2s
Can be used as a farming tool
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sledgehammer-->
<text>
	<id>562</id>
	<name>A flat metal head can do damage to a devastating degree, due to its large size. Certainly useful for various demolition purposes.

Damage: 41-69
Crit Chance: 40%
Block Chance: 15%
Attack Speed: 1.8s
Can dismantle structures and salvage metal plates
</name>
</text>

<!-- Crusader Sword-->
<text>
	<id>563</id>
	<name>In legends, a sword such as this is destined for a great hero. The wielder would be someone of pure heart, chosen by God to wield it against the forces of evil.

Damage: 56-94
Crit Chance: 35%
Block Chance: 25%
Attack Speed: 1.5s
Can chop trees
</name>
</text>

<!-- Frying Pan-->
<text>
	<id>564</id>
	<name>A cast-iron pan purposely built for cooking up hate for your enemies.

Damage: 25-41
Crit Chance: 40%
Block Chance: 35%
Attack Speed: 0.9s
Can Cook: Fried Egg (requires Egg + Campfire), Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes (requires Egg + Tomato + Campfire), Pepper Steak (requires Raw Steak/Raw Rabbit/Raw Chicken + Bell Pepper + Campfire)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Katana-->
<text>
	<id>565</id>
	<name>A single-edged Japanese blade historically used by the samurai class in feudal Japan. Its elegant design is considered both a weapon and a work of art.

Damage: 48-81
Crit Chance: 35%
Block Chance: 25%
Attack Speed: 1.2s
Can chop trees
</name>
</text>

<!-- Barbed Wire Baseball Bat-->
<text>
	<id>566</id>
	<name>A regular baseball bat wrapped in gnarly barbed wire.

Damage: 38-63
Crit Chance: 35%
Block Chance: 20%
Attack Speed: 1s
</name>
</text>

<!-- Chainsaw-->
<text>
	<id>567</id>
	<name>Texas, our Texas! So wonderful, so great!

Damage: 0 (off) / 10 (on)
Crit Chance: 0% (off) / 20% (on)
Block Chance: 0% (off) / 40% (on)
Attack Speed: 0.1s
Can be fueled with gasoline; consumes fuel while active
Can chop trees, dismantle structures, salvage metal plates (requires activation)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Generator-->
<text>
	<id>568</id>
	<name>A portable gasoline-powered generator. Provides enough electricity to power a small home for as long as the fuel lasts.

A heavy generator, requires two hands to carry.
Can be deployed and filled with gasoline
Can be turned on for various electrical applications
</name>
</text>

<!-- Metal Plate-->
<text>
	<id>569</id>
	<name>Metal sheets scrapped from wrecks. Great if you need to do some serious building, otherwise not that useful.

A large metal plate, requires two hands to carry.
Can be crafted: Metal Fence (requires Wood), Reinforce Vehicle (requires Blowtorch + Vehicle)
</name>
</text>

<!-- Secret location reveal-->
<text>
	<id>150</id>
	<name>This is a secret location!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>151</id>
	<name>Call in airdrop!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>152</id>
	<name>Load</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>153</id>
	<name>This vehicle doesn't have a mounted machine gun.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>154</id>
	<name>I can't do that here.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>155</id>
	<name>Please select a difficulty level.
Some unlocks require completion on higher difficulties.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>156</id>
	<name>I need a weapon with a grenade launcher attached.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>157</id>
	<name>Ammo: </name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>158</id>
	<name>I can't do that while I'm sick.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>159</id>
	<name>I'm too weak... can't do that yet.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>160</id>
	<name>I'm bleeding!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>161</id>
	<name>Refuse</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>162</id>
	<name>We have nothing left to say to each other.</name>
</text>

<!-- Bot phrases for commands-->
<text>
	<id>163</id>
	<name>Alright! Let's go!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>164</id>
	<name>I'll watch this area!</name>
</text>

<!-- Phrases for sleeping-->
<text>
	<id>165</id>
	<name>Enemies are nearby. I can't sleep now.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>166</id>
	<name>I'd better sleep at night.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>167</id>
	<name>You can sleep at night. If you are in good condition, you will wake up at 6:00 AM; if you are hungry or thirsty, you will wake up earlier.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>168</id>
	<name>Sleep</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>169</id>
	<name>Conditions are suitable for sleeping.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>170</id>
	<name>It's too cold here. I can't sleep.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>171</id>
	<name>I'm so hungry.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>172</id>
	<name>I'm so thirsty.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>173</id>
	<name>I'm bleeding. I can't do this.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>174</id>
	<name>I need to sleep inside a house.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>175</id>
	<name>I'm not feeling well. I can't sleep.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>176</id>
	<name>I can't sleep during the day.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>177</id>
	<name>I can't sleep.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>178</id>
	<name>Legendary</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>179</id>
	<name>Too close! You'll hit me!</name>
</text>

<!-- Characters -->
<text>
	<id>180</id>
	<name>Xavier "The Pilot"
Equipment: Gorka Pants, Sweater, Pilot Helmet, UMP-45, Flare
Special Skills: Survivor (Level 2), Scouting</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>181</id>
	<name>Xavier "The Pilot"
Unlock Requirement: Find 13 military crash sites in one run
On "Legendary" difficulty</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>182</id>
	<name>Rudolf "The Hunter"
Equipment: IZH-43, Ushanka, 12 Gauge Shells×10, Hunter Knife, Spinning Fishing Rod, Hunting Jacket, Hunting Pants
Special Skills: Hunter (Level 2), Vigilance</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>183</id>
	<name>Rudolf "The Hunter"
Unlock Requirement: Find and kill 3 Albino Deer in one run
On "Legendary" difficulty</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>184</id>
	<name>Taman "The Guard"
Equipment: Police Hat, Orel Jacket, Orel Pants, AKs-74u, Energy Drink
Special Skills: Marksman (Level 2), Ammo Seeker</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>185</id>
	<name>Taman "The Guard"
Unlock Requirement: Kill a "Tank" using the Humvee's mounted machine gun
On "Legendary" difficulty</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>186</id>
	<name>Daria "The Scientist"
Equipment: Work Pants, Apron, Shirt, Tetracycline, Empty Blood Bag, Vitamins, Morphine, Bandage×3
Special Skills: Vitality (Level 2), Sprinter</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>187</id>
	<name>Daria "The Scientist"
Unlock Requirement: Reach the Fifth Island
On "Legendary" difficulty</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>188</id>
	<name>Sharpen (+25%)</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>189</id>
	<name>Desert Eagle Pistol
Unlock Requirement: Simultaneously wear a Cowboy Hat, a Shirt, and carry a Magnum Revolver
On "Regular" difficulty or higher
Current Progress:</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>190</id>
	<name>Desert Eagle Pistol
Unlocked
Spawns in: Bunkers, Gun Stores</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>191</id>
	<name>Katana
Unlock Requirement: Kill 100 Infected with a Knife
On "Legendary" difficulty
Current Progress:</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>192</id>
	<name>Katana
Unlocked
Spawns in: Gun Stores</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>193</id>
	<name>The weapon is sharper now.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>194</id>
	<name>This weapon cannot be sharpened.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>195</id>
	<name>Craft Rope</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>196</id>
	<name>I need 3 Rags to make it.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>197</id>
	<name>Follow me!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>198</id>
	<name>Patrol here!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>199</id>
	<name>Go away!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>200</id>
	<name>Hello, survivor!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>201</id>
	<name>I can't do that here.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>202</id>
	<name>There are enemies nearby!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>203</id>
	<name>I think I can jump the car across.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>204</id>
	<name>Are you sure you want to jump to the broken bridge?
	You will not be able to return here. Many dangers await on the other side!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>205</id>
	<name>Hello!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>206</id>
	<name>Hey, survivor! Can you help us?</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>207</id>
	<name>Don't shoot! We're friends.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>208</id>
	<name>Hi</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>209</id>
	<name>Thanks!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>210</id>
	<name>Hey, survivor! We've heard about you!
	You've helped a lot of people in need.
	We want to help you.
	Take this, and may God bless you.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>611</id>
	<name>I learned something from this!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>612</id>
	<name>Read</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>613</id>
	<name>I feel invincible, but sadly, I'm not.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>614</id>
	<name>minutes</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>615</id>
	<name>Craft Tarpaulin</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>616</id>
	<name>Supply Cache</name>
</text>

<!-- Difficulty descriptions-->
<text>
	<id>617</id>
	<name>• Hunger and thirst deplete slowly
• Mild weather
• Reduced NPC damage to player
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>618</id>
	<name>• Normal hunger and thirst depletion
• Normal weather
• Normal NPC damage to player
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>619</id>
	<name>• Hunger and thirst deplete faster
• Cold weather
• Increased NPC damage to player
• More infected in some areas
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>620</id>
	<name>• Hunger and thirst deplete faster
• Extreme weather
• NPC ranged attacks can score headshots
• More powerful infected in some areas
• Unexplored areas are hidden from the minimap
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>621</id>
	<name>Start
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>622</id>
	<name>Are you sure you want to proceed to the Fifth Island?
	You will not be able to return.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>623</id>
	<name>Are you sure you want to proceed to the Fifth Island?
	You will not be able to return.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>624</id>
	<name>Fishing rod durability is too low.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>625</id>
	<name>Craft Molotov Cocktail
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>626</id>
	<name>Molotov Cocktail and Rope
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>627</id>
	<name>Rag x3 = Rope
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>628</id>
	<name>Whiskey + Flare = Molotov Cocktail
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>629</id>
	<name>Cache Supplies
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>630</id>
	<name>Sack × 2 = Tarpaulin
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>631</id>
	<name>Tarpaulin + Wood = Supply Cache
Supplies hidden inside will not disappear
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>632</id>
	<name>Mike "The Designer"
Unlock Requirement: Reach the Unknown Island
On "Legendary" difficulty
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>633</id>
	<name>Mike "The Designer"
Equipment: Awesome Hoodie, Work Pants, Sword, Vector SMG, Energy Drink×4, .45 ACP Ammo×60
Special Skills: Marksman, Scouting, Sprinter, Lethal Strike</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>634</id>
	<name>Medical Tape
Unlock Requirement: Escape with Emilio "The Doctor", Billy "The Radical", or Dave "The Boxer"</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>635</id>
	<name>Lighter
Unlock Requirement: Escape with Lee "The Madman", Sergey "The Slav", or John "The Biker"</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>636</id>
	<name>Smoke Grenade
Unlock Requirement: Escape with Ganzo "The Dragon", Tom "The Survivor", or Garry "The Veteran"</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>637</id>
	<name>Laser Sight
Unlock Requirement: Escape with Kate "The Traveler", Jasmine "The Lumberjack", or Aika "The War Correspondent"</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>638</id>
	<name>Keycard
Unlock Requirement: Escape with Xavier "The Pilot", Rudolf "The Hunter", Taman "The Guard", or Daria "The Scientist"</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>639</id>
	<name>...Repeat! We hear you! We'll be there in one day! Hang on...</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>640</id>
	<name>Try using the radio to contact nearby survivors?</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>641</id>
	<name>Smoke</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>642</id>
	<name>Protect</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>643</id>
	<name>Fertilize</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>644</id>
	<name>Items</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>645</id>
	<name>Medical Tape
Unlocked
Spawns in: Hospitals, Cities</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>646</id>
	<name>Lighter
Unlocked
Spawns in: Fire Stations, Warehouses</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>647</id>
	<name>Smoke Grenade
Unlocked
Spawns in: Bunkers, Military Bases</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>648</id>
	<name>Laser Sight
Unlocked
Spawns in: Bunkers, Military Bases</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>649</id>
	<name>Keycard
Unlocked
Carried by infected officers</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>650</id>
	<name>I need fire to light this.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>651</id>
	<name>I can't sleep. I can't miss the rescue helicopter.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>652</id>
	<name>I can't go into the bunker. I can't miss the rescue helicopter.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>653</id>
	<name>Hey, survivor! I'm Boris, welcome aboard!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>654</id>
	<name>Nadia, head east, signal 4316!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>655</id>
	<name>Survivor has escaped.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>656</id>
	<name>I need to get back to the radio!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>657</id>
	<name>Unknown Island #</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>658</id>
	<name>Are you ready to use the elevator?
	You will not be able to return.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>659</id>
	<name>This door requires a Keycard.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>660</id>
	<name>I need a plant.</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>661</id>
	<name>Keyboard (WASD)</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>662</id>
	<name>Thanks!</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>663</id>
	<name>Craft Makeshift Suppressor</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>664</id>
	<name>Combine</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>665</id>
	<name>Build Bed</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>666</id>
	<name>Bob "Hooded Bandit"
Unlock Requirement: Unlock all characters
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>667</id>
	<name>Bob "Hooded Bandit"
Equipment: Trench Coat, Work Pants, Gorka Helmet, Bulletproof Vest, AKM, 7.62x39mm Ammo×50, Rifle Sling
Special Skills: Marksman (Level 2), Scouting (Level 2)
Special Quirks: Reputation -100, starts with a bandit buddy
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>668</id>
	<name>• Includes all Legendary difficulty settings
• All characters start from scratch
• All positive modifiers forcibly disabled
• All negative modifiers forcibly enabled
• Extended features disabled
</name>
</text>

<!-- Protective Boot Covers-->
<text>
	<id>700</id>
	<name>A pair of boots with excellent airtightness and waterproofing.

Part of a complete protective suit.
When worn, allows ignoring ground acid.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Protective Gloves-->
<text>
	<id>701</id>
	<name>A pair of gloves with excellent airtightness and waterproofing.

Part of a complete protective suit.
When worn, looting zombies has no penalty.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class A Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>702</id>
	<name>An airtight Class A Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be sealed to block contaminated air for 2 minutes (requires full protection).</name>
</text>

<!-- Class C Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>703</id>
	<name>A basic protection Class C Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).</name>
</text>

<!-- 12 Gauge Drum Mag-->
<text>
	<id>704</id>
	<name>A drum magazine that holds 20 rounds of 12 Gauge.

Fits on: Saiga-12k
</name>
</text>

<!-- Paint Can-->
<text>
	<id>705</id>
	<name>Can change the color of clothes, pants, backpacks, and vehicles.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Headlamp-->
<text>
	<id>706</id>
	<name>A hands-free lighting device worn on the head with an adjustable strap.

Heat: +1
Requires a battery to operate
</name>
</text>

<!-- Night Vision Goggles-->
<text>
	<id>707</id>
	<name>Battery-powered Night Vision Goggles for intensifying images in low-light environments. Comes with a headstrap.

Heat: +1
Requires a battery to operate
</name>
</text>

<!-- AI-2 Medkit-->
<text>
	<id>708</id>
	<name>The original AI-2 Cold War-era medical kit designed to protect Soviet citizens and military personnel from chemical, biological, radiological, and nuclear threats.

Health: +50
Effect: Stops bleeding and temporarily grants immunity to radiation
Duration: 120 sec
</name>
</text>

<!-- Dog Crate-->
<text>
	<id>709</id>
	<name>A weathered dog kennel with chew marks on the door. Tucked inside, a brown, short-haired dog naps peacefully, curled up on a bed of hay.

Can release or recall your dog
Your dog can fetch the first item it picks up
</name>
</text>

<!-- Adrenaline-->
<text>
	<id>710</id>
	<name>A psychostimulant adrenaline used for enhancing attention, cognition, and physical performance.

Health: +10
Effect: Increases Headshot Chance, Block Chance, and Movement Speed by 20% each
Duration: 120 sec
Max Stack: 3
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class A Military CBRN Suit-->
<text>
	<id>711</id>
	<name>A military-grade protective suit, allowing attachment of a Ghillie suit, Kevlar vest, or M Heavy Armor.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).
Can be sealed to block contaminated air for 2 minutes (requires full protection).</name>
</text>

<!-- Advanced Map-->
<text>
	<id>712</id>
	<name>Specifies the type of next island and reveals the next island's map.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Class B Protective Suit-->
<text>
	<id>713</id>
	<name>A radiation-proof Class B Protective Suit.

Effect activates when durability is above 50%. Full protection requires gloves and boots.
Rainproof, Radiation-proof, Biohazard-proof (requires full protection).</name>
</text>

<!-- Deer Hide-->
<text>
	<id>714</id>
	<name>A supple, durable, and lightweight leather known for its exceptional softness and breathability. Deerskin is considered a luxury leather.

Can be crafted: Bed (requires Wood)</name>
</text>

<!-- C-MAG 5.45-->
<text>
	<id>715</id>
	<name>A double drum magazine that holds 95 rounds of 5.45x39.

Fits on: AK-74, AKs-74u
</name>
</text>

<!-- Spiked Collar-->
<text>
	<id>716</id>
	<name>Commands your dog to actively attract and attack zombies.

May fail against high-threat targets.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pannier Bag-->
<text>
	<id>717</id>
	<name>Your dog will automatically pick up items of the same type it is carrying.

Auto-picked items cannot be carried to the next island.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Egg-->
<text>
	<id>718</id>
	<name>Organic eggs. High in protein, come from country hens that are free to roam outside during the day and are housed safely and securely in hen houses at night.

Hunger: +10
Thirst: +10
Max Stack: 3
Ingredient for: Fried Egg, Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes
</name>
</text>

<!-- Raw Chicken-->
<text>
	<id>719</id>
	<name>Uncooked poultry, a good source of protein.

Hunger: +25
Thirst: +10
Consuming has a 50% chance to cause sickness
Can be cooked over a fire
Ingredient for: Pepper Steak
</name>
</text>

<!-- Cooked Chicken-->
<text>
	<id>720</id>
	<name>Raw chicken roasted over a campfire.

Hunger: +35
Thirst: +10
Health: +20
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pistol Sight-->
<text>
	<id>721</id>
	<name>A basic RDS pistol sight.

Spread: -1
Headshot Chance: +5%
Fits on: FNX, Glock, Desert Eagle
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pistol Suppressor-->
<text>
	<id>722</id>
	<name>A pistol suppressor of a high caliber; should silence smaller calibers as well.

Provides sound suppression
Fits on: FNX, Colt 1911, Glock, Desert Eagle, MAC-10, Mini-UZI, MP5K, UMP-45, Bizon, Vector
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pistol Flashlight-->
<text>
	<id>723</id>
	<name>A tactical light used in conjunction with a pistol to illuminate the target.

Fits on: FNX, Colt 1911, Glock
</name>
</text>

<!-- Fried Egg-->
<text>
	<id>724</id>
	<name>A fried egg, sunny-side up. Simple and delicious.

Hunger: +20
Thirst: +5
Health: +5
Immunity: +5
</name>
</text>

<!-- Pepper Steak-->
<text>
	<id>725</id>
	<name>This classic stir-fry combines tender, thinly sliced meat with crisp bell peppers in a savory dish. Garnish and serve.

Hunger: +60
Thirst: +15
Health: +30
Immunity: +30
</name>
</text>

<!-- Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes-->
<text>
	<id>726</id>
	<name>A simple but super comforting dish that's popular in home cooking, made by scrambling eggs on a hot pan and adding diced tomatoes.

Hunger: +35
Thirst: +20
Health: +10
Immunity: +10
</name>
</text>

<!-- Spotlight-->
<text>
	<id>727</id>
	<name>A searchlight tripod stand and the headlights that go on top. Can illuminate large areas when powered by a generator.

Provides illumination, requires a generator to function
Can be deployed in bunkers
</name>
</text>

<!-- Earthworms-->
<text>
	<id>728</id>
	<name>Common earthworms, excellent bait for fishing.

Hunger: +5
Immunity: -10
Max Stack: 10
Can repair fishing rod durability
</name>
</text>

<!-- Improvised VOG-25 Grenade-->
<text>
	<id>729</id>
	<name>A modified hand grenade version of the VOG-25 grenade round. A homemade Russian ingenuity.

Explodes on impact
</name>
</text>

<!-- FNX-45 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>730</id>
	<name>A nimble pistol favored by many.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 21-35             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 9
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 15
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Colt 1911 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>731</id>
	<name>"God created men, Colt made them equal."
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 7
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Magnum Revolver (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>732</id>
	<name>One of the most powerful handguns in the world.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 34-56             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 15
Run Penalty: 3              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 6
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Amphibia S (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>733</id>
	<name>A pistol designed for underwater combat by naval personnel.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 11-19             Spread: 4
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 9
Run Penalty: 3              Ammo: .22 LR
Mag Capacity: 10
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Glock 17 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>734</id>
	<name>A semi-automatic pistol made in Austria.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 15-25             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9mm
Mag Capacity: 18
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sawn-off IZH-43 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>735</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the IZH-43 shotgun.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 22-188           Spread: 13
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 20
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 12 Gauge
Mag Capacity: 2
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sawn-off Mosin (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>736</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the Mosin-Nagant rifle.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 12
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 25
Run Penalty: 1              Ammo: 7.62x54mmR
Mag Capacity: 5
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Engraved Colt (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>737</id>
	<name>A meticulously engraved Colt pistol.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 5
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .45 ACP
Mag Capacity: 12
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sawn-off Rossi M92 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>738</id>
	<name>"This is wild country out here, ma'am." -Josh Randall
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 34-56             Spread: 11
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 17
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 7
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- PM Makarov (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>739</id>
	<name>Small, lightweight, favored by Soviet officers.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9x18mm
Mag Capacity: 8
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- PB Silent Pistol (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>740</id>
	<name>A Soviet integrally suppressed, semi-automatic pistol developed for covert special operations by the KGB and Spetsnaz.
Integrated Suppressor
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 9
Aim Speed: 4               Recoil: 8
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 9x18mm
Mag Capacity: 8
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Desert Eagle (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>741</id>
	<name>A favorite among firearm collectors.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 30-50             Spread: 6
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 13
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .357
Mag Capacity: 9
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- M79 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>742</id>
	<name>It might look outdated, but it's still effective.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 45-540           Spread: 8
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 6
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: 40mm Grenade
Mag Capacity: 1
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Sawn-off Blaze (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>743</id>
	<name>A sawn-off version of the Blaze double-barreled rifle.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 71-119           Spread: 12
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 10
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .308
Mag Capacity: 2
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Longhorn (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>744</id>
	<name>Single-shot break-action hunting pistol. Suited for hunting game, comes with an integrated scope.
Integrated Scope
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 79-131           Spread: 1
Aim Speed: 2               Recoil: 25
Run Penalty: 2              Ammo: .308
Mag Capacity: 1
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- MAC-10 (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>745</id>
	<name>One of the world-famous firearms made in the USA.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 15-25             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 30          Ammo: 9mm
Fire Rate: 650 RPM
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Mini-UZI (Duplicate)-->
<text>
	<id>746</id>
	<name>A lightweight submachine gun manufactured in Israel.
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
Damage: 18-30             Spread: 10
Aim Speed: 3               Recoil: 2
Run Penalty: 0              Reload Time: 2s
Mag Capacity: 22          Ammo: .45 ACP
Fire Rate: 600 RPM
 ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶ ̶
</name>
</text>

<!-- Equal Exchange (Moved to end)-->
<text>
	<id>64</id>
	<name>AK Grip 🔄 Rail Grip   5.45 Suppressor 🔄 5.56 Suppressor
GP-25 Launcher 🔄 M203 Launcher
40mm Grenade 🔄 VOG Grenade
Quick-Draw Mag 🔄 Bandolier   ACOG 🔄 PSO-1
Cleaning Kit 🔄 Blowtorch   Pepsi 🔄 Nota-Cola
1PN51 NVD 🔄 PVS-4 NVD
C-MAG (5.45) 🔄 C-MAG (5.56)
7.62×39 Drum 🔄 12 Gauge Drum
</name>
</text>

<!-- Item Locker-->
<text>
	<id>65</id>
	<name>Carry Capacity: +6
Items stored inside can be carried over to the next game.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Build Mode-->
<text>
	<id>66</id>
	<name>When deploying, pressing X to cancel no longer returns the item, but stores it inside.
</name>
</text>

<!-- EXP Shop-->
<text>
	<id>67</id>
	<name>The random item list refreshes daily at 00:00.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>747</id>
	<name>A highly powerful explosive device, once placed and activated with a timer, continuously attracts zombies. It explodes after a 15-second countdown.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>748</id>
	<name>A red hat full of festive atmosphere
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>749</id>
	<name>Gifts from winter
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>750</id>
	<name>If you have an appetite and no moral compass, you can eat this in an emergency.

Satiety +15, Hydration +10, Health -10, 100% chance of getting sick after consumption. 
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>751</id>
	<name>If you have an appetite and no moral compass, you can eat this in an emergency.

Satiety +25, Hydration +10, Health -10, 50% chance of getting sick after consumption.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>752</id>
	<name>Carrying capacity +2
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>753</id>
	<name>Carry capacity +1, Tool storage slots +3. Can store knives, matches, lighters, flares, and military water bottles.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>754</id>
	<name>Carrying capacity +1 Medical storage compartments +3 Can store any medical supplies and any medications
</name>
</text>

<!-- Weapon Storage Case (ID 755)-->
<text>
	<id>755</id>
	<name>A sturdy, reinforced container designed specifically for secure firearm storage. Features protective foam padding to keep your weapon safe from damage and corrosion.

Can store or retrieve one primary weapon.
The sealed case protects your firearm from the elements and prevents durability loss over time.
Perfect for keeping a spare weapon or saving a favorite firearm for future use.
</name>
</text>

<!-- Waist Holster (ID 756)-->
<text>
	<id>756</id>
	<name>A comfortable, adjustable holster designed to be worn on the waist. Keeps a secondary weapon secure yet easily accessible.

Can be attached to the waist as an accessory to carry an additional secondary firearm.
Quick-draw design allows for faster switching to your sidearm.
</name>
</text>

<text>
	<id>757</id>
	<name>Thickened work gloves, providing warmth, comfort and excellent cold protection.

Heat +3
When equipped, looting zombies has no penalty
</name>
</text>

</list>

